Alwasi Muhrijafiatna

Bandung, Indonesia 40232 | linkedin.com/in/alwasi-muhrijafiatna-757b9a27b/ | +62895359776598 | alwasiwasi29@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

An undergraduate student in Educational Electrical Engineering with a temporary GPA of 3.50-4.00 and is very interested in the concentration of Electrical and Installation with a total of 3 years experience as an aviation electronics student at SMKN 12 Bandung. Obtained competency certification in the field of aviation and has attended Industrial Work Practices with Aviation Maintenance Expertise, PT. Dewata Angkasa, Bandung.

EXPERIENCES

Himpunan Mahasiswa Elektro

(June 2022 - June 2023)

Chairman of the Sub-Division of Telecommunication Engineering Development Creating a plan and instructing the employees to carry out the work program

Steering Committee Telecommunication Training

(January 2023 - May 2023)

Provided actionable recommendations to the committee on how to optimize event planning process, resulting in a 20% increase in attendance and a 30% reduction in event planning time

Project Manager Workshop Telecommunication

(September 2021 - February 2022)

Directing and ensuring the committee prepares and carries out the work program until completion

PT Dewata Angkasa

apprenticeship

(April 2019 - July 2019)

Responsible to analyzing, troubleshooting and repairing aircraft components such as booster pumps, AC generators, DC generators, hydraulic pumps and others

EDUCATION

Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia

Bachelors Pendidikan Teknik Elektro

(September 2020 - Present)

3.50/4.00

Creating several assignment projects such as designing a home electrical circuit, IoT-based device, and an automatic calculator using the Python programming language

SMKN 12 Bandung

(June 2017 - June 2020)

High School Aviation Electronics · Electrical Wiring · Avionics

85

PROJECTS

Design and Development of Automatic Trash Bin based on IoT

(May 2022 - June 2020)

created a miniature IoT based automatic gate using an ESP32 microcontroller, and ultrasonic sensor to measure the distance

Design of FTTH Access Network Using Gigabit Passive Optical Network (GPON) in Setiabudhi Terrace Housing Estate.

(April 2023 -May 2023) Created the design of Fiber to the home (FTTH) network for 45 house in Setiabudhi Terrace Housing Estate

Simple Hartley Oscillator Resonance Frequency Calculator

(March 2023 - April 2023)

created a simple calculator with 3 inputs using python language

SKILLS

Native Bahasa Indonesia, Aviation Electronics, Electrical Telecommuncation, Ms Office.